const questions= [
{
question: "What is the name of Pam's first fiance?",
options: ["Jim", "Daryl", "Roy", "Michael"],
answer: "Roy"
},

{
question: "Where are Pam and and Jim married?",
options: ["Scranton", "Idaho", "Niagra Falls", "Chili's"],
answer: "Niagra Falls"
},

{
question: "How does Meredith become hospitalized?",
options: ["She is bitten by a bat", "She is hit by a car", "She is set on fire", "She gets alcohol poisoning"],
answer: "She is hit by a car"
},

{
question: "What is Dwight's brother's name?",
options: ["Jonah", "Brendan", "Kemper", "Mose"],
answer: "Mose"
},

{
question: "How many siblings does Jim have?",
options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
answer: "2"
},

{
question: "What is the first ever prank filmed on The Office?",
options: ["Stapler in Jell-O", "Mega-Desk", "Faxes from future Dwight", "Spool of wire"],
answer: "Stapler in Jell-O"
},

{
question: "What restaurant chain is Pam banned from?",
options: ["TGI Fridays", "Red-Robin" "Applebees" "Chilis"],
answer: "Chilis"
},

{
question: "What is the name of Jan's daughter?",
options: ["Meredith", "Astird", "Astrid", "Ariel"],
answer: "Astrid"
},

{
question: "What is Phylis's husband's donation to Casino Night?",
options: ["Full size refridgerator", "Mini refridgerator", "Air conditioner", "Water heater"],
answer: "Mini refridgerator"
},

{
question: "At one point, Creed Bratton implies that he killed a man. What was the man's name?",
options: ["Creed Bratton", "Corbin Dallas", "Bob vance", "Todd Packer"],
answer: "Creed Bratton"
},
]
